Privacy Policy
--------------

This Policy governs our processing of your personal data and the way in which we deal with other data that is not personal information as defined in the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation EU2016/679 (“GDPR”). The term “processing” is used as defined in the GDPR. It includes collection, storage, and all of the ways we use, and allow you to use, personal information, when we provide our services. You are the data controller under the GDPR of the personal information you provide to us as part of your Account Data (see below).

#### Your Files

This is the section of this Policy that covers the actual encrypted files that you upload, access and share using our service. When you upload a file, it is already encrypted at your device, so we do not know whether it is personal to you or someone else, relates to a business or some other organisation, or what it contains. All Your Files remain encrypted at all times while they are on our system. They are never received, stored or otherwise dealt with by us in unencrypted form because any decryption takes place only on your device or that of another user to whom you have provided the file links and keys that are created when you give them access. Your Files are therefore not personal data under the GDPR since they are never held by Vault.ooo in a form that is information about an identified or identifiable natural person. We collect Your Files because that is necessary for us to provide our end-to-end encrypted cloud storage and collaboration services. We keep Your Files while you are subscribed to our services but subject to our suspension and termination rights set out in our Terms. You must maintain copies of Your Files. We do not make any guarantees that there will be no loss of data or the services will be bug free. If you lose a file link, access to the file can not be restored.

#### User Data

We don't collect or log any data of our users, especially no IP adresses, in respect for privacy. We only have files uploaded by our users.

#### Purchases made on Vault.ooo

When purchasing on vault.ooo, payment information provided by the payment service provider, time of purchase, delivery email, how long the purchased product will be active and the email address needed to assign the shared drive in Google Drive will be stored.

#### Changes to our Policy

We may make changes to this Policy in the future. Therefore, you should check this policy for changes before each use of the service.

vault.ooo
---------
